SAH KRITIK

WEB DEVELOPER



- +91 7021245436
- kritiksahco@gmail.com
- Mumbai / Bangalore, India
- in <u>linkedin.com/in/kritiksah/</u>
- kritik.servicesstrategy.com
- youtube.com/itrebels
- English, Hindi & Marathi

SKILLS

- Problem Solving
- Node JS/javascript knowledge
- React, Redux, Next. js experience
- Basic understanding of web3 tech
- Solidity, Ethers.js, foundry EVM
- Git/Github & version control
- Project Management Tools(Jira)
- Good Communication
- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Tailwind experience
- CMS like Wordpress.
- Photoshop
- Video Editing

PROFILE

Greetings, my name is Kritik Sah, and I am a 23-year-old frontend web developer. I possess a strong zeal for expanding my knowledge and skillset within the realm of web3 and blockchain technology.

open for: Frontend lead, Solidity developer / Auditing, Dev. rel. Community management in web3

EXPERIENCE

FRONTEND DEVELOPER (NEXTJS, WEB3)

Omega Athena Technology Private Ltd / DAOstruct 2023 - Present

- Learned and improved my react, nextis skills.
- Learned about the web3 ecosystem, and technology like
 Ethereum, smart contracts, and wallets.
- Attended a lot of. web3 events and made some valuable connections.
- As a founding front-end developer, I learned to manage deliverables and get better results.

SDE I - FRONTEND (REACTJS, REDUX)

Intellihealth Solutions Pvt. Ltd. / Truemeds 2022 - 2023

- Intellihealth Solutions Private Limited also known as Truemeds, It
 is a digital pharmacy and consultancy it was a product-based
 startup.
- I have worked on admin and other management portals from the catalog to incomplete orders.
- I learned react.js and improved my skill while working with truemeds.

EDUCATION

HIGHER SECONDARY SCHOOL

Maharashtra Board

2016 - 2018

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE (MATHEMATICS)

Mumbai University

2018 - 2021

AWARDS

- Polygon Road to Web3 Hackathon
 Winner Badge.
- Polygon Road to Web3 Hackathon
 Participant Badge
- Web3 Twitter Buidler moralis

PROJECTS

- Portfolio
- ServicesStrategy.com
- infinitelearning.org.in
- Fitndur
- Cocktail recipe application
- NASA PID Next 13 application
- Bank Dapp with smart contract
- NFT Gating website(Dapp)

LEARNING

- Smart contract development & testing
- · Professional video editing
- Videography
- · Community building
- · How to enjoy my life ;p

JR. FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Tonic WorldWide pvt. Ltd.

2021 - 2022

- Since I am a self-taught developer, I gained so much confidence and knowledge while working on my first IT Job.
- I worked on many web projects and built 100+ mailers in just 6 months.
- I improved so many different skills, like blogging, using phpMyAdmin, and Photoshop, and Cleaning some backend codes in PHP and MySQL (I still don't know much about this though), I mostly worked on frontend technology like HTML, CSS, bootstrap, jquery & javascript.

FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER/ GRAPHIC DESIGNER

IT Rebels(Self Employed)

2018 - Present

- At the end of my first year, I started my freelancing journey with fiverr.com in which I started with basic graphic designing and then I improved my portfolio with each order I received.
- It was a tough journey since no one was there to guide me, but still, I am happy that I took my first step there.

ASSOCIATE VIDEO EDITOR

Rangrez studio

2018 - 2019

- It was my first job, where I learned to use Photoshop and video editing software like adobe premier pro.
- Here I discovered my most important lesson, which is I can learn what I love to do, there are people who will pay me for this.

CERTIFICATIONS

FREECODECAMP.ORG CERTIFICATIONS:

- <u>Responsive Web Design</u>: All about HTML, CSS, and the foundation of web development.
- <u>JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures</u>: Foundation of javascript with Data structure and Algorithms.
- <u>Front End Development Libraries</u>: In the Front End Development Libraries Certification, I learned how to style our site quickly with Bootstrap & how to create powerful Single Page Applications (SPAs) with React and Redux.
- Data Visualization: Data Visualization with D3.

WORKING ON

- IT Rebels DAO (Onboard 1000 devs in web3) currently 7.1k subs on
- 13+ dapp projects for teaching purpose
- Myself so i can be a better human being.

UDEMY COURSE CERTIFICATIONS:

- The Complete 2023 Web Development Bootcamp Dr. Angela Yu
- Linux for Absolute Beginners!
- Linux BASH Shell Terminal Command Basics
- Python: Master Programming and Development with 15 Projects

ALCHEMY UNIVERSITY CERTIFICATIONS:

- JavaScript Fundamentals
- Ethereum Developer Bootcamp

METACRAFTERS ACADEMY CERTIFICATIONS:

- ETH PROOF: Beginner EVM Course
- ETH PROOF: Intermediate EVM Course
- ETH PROOF: Advance EVM Course